Adam Yonah Trachtman

Full Stack Developer

052-404-8570 | yonah.trachtman@gmail.com Github | LinkedIn | personal portfolio

SUMMARY

I'm a Full-Stack Developer and I have knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, Python, and the most up-to-date technologies. I have worked on several projects using React, Redux, Node.JS, Postgres, and Typescript. I look forward to using all the knowledge I gained from my studies to contribute to a team.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python, OOP, SQL, Flask, Django, Javascript, React, Redux, Typescript, Git, Postgres.

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Text-Based RPG- Github

A text-based RPG game made in Python and OOP for a Hackathon, version control was with Git and GitHub

I built this project as part of a team in order to solidify my basis in OOP

- Implemented Items and Equipment into the game to add a sense of scaling
- Implemented stats screen in order to be able to check your character's progress
- Troubleshooting and bug testing every time a new feature was implemented

Collaborative Online Whiteboard- Github/Deployed

An online whiteboard made in React with Redux and Typescript and databases using Node.js and Postgres

- Implemented user login in CRUD
- Implemented databases for users and whiteboards
- Troubleshooting and bug testing every time a new feature was implemented

EXPERIENCE

Customer Support Representative

Jerusalem, Israel

TCS Telecom

06/2020 - 06/2021

- Handled calls and emails from customers with speed and efficiency to understand and fix their issue
- Troubleshoot issues for customers in order to help with customer satisfaction and retention
- Served as a stand-in sales rep during the summer rush
- Worked with other customer support reps with the same customer based on work scheduled

Armored Core Communications Specialist

Many, Israel 03/2017 - 12/2019

IDF

Preformed daily inspections of communications equipment to make sure everything was working

- Worked with a team for organization and testing of equipment
- Guarded equipment and took inventory on a regular basis

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development	t, Python	and Javas	Script program
D	- ·		

Ramat Gan, Israel 05/2024 - 09/2024

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

Remote, Germany 01/2024 - 02/2024

Frontend Development Hands-on Training Program Kreativstorm

LANGUAGES

English - Native, Hebrew - Intermediate